可以朝铁锅的表面泼一点水
You can be sure the wok is at the correct temperature
水滴突然会跳起舞来
by sprinkling water on the surface.
然后它就蒸发掉了。
The droplets should dance before evaporating.
跳的是芭蕾还是伦巴？
Yes,ballet or rumba?
完美
Perfecto!
爸爸，我们有个建议
Hey dad,look. We got a deal for you.
让店里送馅饼来吧，钱我们来付。
If you'll just order pizza we'll pay for it.
要双层馅的。
Two toppings!
你们俩的意思就是你们的老爸没有能力
Are you guys saying that you have no faith in your old dad's ability
做中国菜？
to cook a simple Chinese dinner?
是这样。
Yep!
亲爱的。孩子们。
Hi honey!
妈妈。
Hi mum
什么着火了？
Hi guys. What's burning?
我！
Me.
谁要是对我的烹调手艺再说三道四的，
If anyone says one more thing about my cooking,
我就甩手不干了。
I may just forget the whole thing.
可是你。
Hey (mouth covered up)
没有人再说你一个字。
No one's going to say a word.
今天做什么吃的？
What are we going to have?
是牛肉泥。
Packed beef.
是吗？
Yum.
对不起，我晚了，我在安妮家。
Sorry I'm late. I was over at Annie's.
是你的新朋友？
Oh your new friend?
Carol，我没有见过你穿过这件衣服。
Oh Carol,I don't remember that sweater.
对，这不是我的，是安妮借给我的。
Oh! No! It's not mine. It's Annie's. She loaned it to me.
噢，快叫警察，书呆子赶时髦了。
Oh call the nerd police. She's out of uniform again.
Mike!
Mike！
你化过妆了吗？
Are you wearing make up?
就擦了点底粉香粉胭脂口红眼影什么的。
Oh just a little base,powder,blush,lipstick,mascara and eye liner.
安妮的？
Annie's?
她说只要色彩运用得我会显得很漂亮。
Yeah. She says with the right color and shading,I have a beautiful face.
你知道，她是对的。
Oh you know,she's right.
Mike，你省着点去取笑你那些朋友吧，
Mike,shut up! You don't see me making fun of your friends.
尤其是说话带吞音的。
Even the ones that drool.
好了，孩子们，吃一顿美餐以后火气就全熄灭了。
You guys will be a little less hostile after some crispy friend duck lips.
幸亏今晚我没有时间和他纠缠不清。
I'm just glad that I won't be around here with Him tonight.
哦？
Oh?
安妮和我准备出去，如果可以的话。
Yeah. Annie and I are going out. If that's Ok?
Carol，你和朋友出去之前总是先向我们介绍的。
Well Carol,usually we know your friends before you go out with them.
这有什么好介绍的，她是啦啦队长，
Well what's to know. She's a cheerleader;
是戏剧组的，非常风趣，人缘也很好。
she's on the drama club,very funny and very popular.
那她为什么老缠着你不放？
So what's she hanging around with you for?
Mike!
Mike！
说话的是他！不是我。
Hey,I didn't say it. He did.
可口气挺象你。
Sorry,it sounded like you.
我可以走了吗？
So is it Ok?
你们打算去哪？
Where will you be going?
去买耳环，我的耳朵刚穿了眼。我能走了吗？
Shopping for ear rings,since I just got my ears pierced.
哦！
Oh!
好了么？
So is it Ok?
当然能，不过晚上回家当心点。
Sure. Just be careful walking after dark.
噢，放心，我们不走路，
Oh don't worry. We won't be walking.
安妮自己开车。
Annie drives.
安妮自己开车？
听见了。
I heard.
顺便让她给我带几个汉堡包好吗？
Hey do you think she could pick some burgers up for us on the way over.
-= Subripped by Susie Shi =-       2007.07.22
Carol穿耳朵的事应该是我带她去，
I was going to take Carol to get her ears pierced.
就给她穿一只。
At least one ear.
好了，亲爱的，要是能让你高兴，
Well honey. If it makes you feel any better,
你该带我去穿我的耳朵。
you can take me to get my ears pierced.
噢，我没开玩笑，Jason。
I'm serious Jason.
可是听你的口气
Well what I'm hearing is that uh..
我总觉得你之所以不愉快是因为
I think you're a little bothered by the fact that
Carol交了个对她很有点影响力的朋友。
Carol is actually making a friend who has some real influence on her.
这话你可说错了，大夫。
How wrong you are doctor.
我希望她的朋友越多越好，
I want Carol to have plenty of friends.
但是不能够交个不正经的。
I just wish she'd pick someone who wasn't a slut.
行了，Maggie，
Come on Maggie.
可是那姑娘你还没有见过呢。
You haven't even met the little tramp.
她把Carol都打扮得成公主了。你还为她辩护。
You're defending a girl who makes our daughter up to look like Prince.
公主不是挺受欢迎吗？
Prince is very popular.
我反正是为孩子着想，没别的。
I know,I know. I'm just worried about her. That's all.
Carol的朋友没一个像她这么爱交际。
I mean Carol has never had a friend before who is so social.
Carol已经到了该有点不听话的年龄了，
Well Carol is also at the age when she is going to rebel a little.
包括她挑选父母亲不一定赞成的朋友。
And that may include picking some friends her parents might not approve of.
对。Mike的父母亲将会是一种什么样的心情呢？
Think how the parents of Mike's friends must feel.
爸爸妈妈，明天见。
Hey,mum,dad,I'll see you in the morning.
好。
Ok.
明天？啊！
Morning! Wo!
慢着，Mike。
Hold it Mike.
你要去哪？
Where are you going?
波拿刚才来电话说他父母亲今晚不在家
Boner just called,and his parents don't want him home alone tonight cause they're out.
所以我去陪他一起过夜。
So I'm gonna go spend the night at his place.
你连自己都要人照顾。
You're baby sitting Boner?
可总得有人去啊。
Hey,somebody's got to.
这种事你怎么事先不跟我们说？
Mike,shouldn't you tell us these things first?
我刚才不是说了吗？
That's what I just did mum.
不不，这话成了马后炮了。
No,no. That's not how it works.
你的意思是说我不能去了？！
Are you guys actually saying that I can't go?
一点不错！
Very good.
爸爸！妈妈你去劝劝他吧！
Dad! Mum,can you talk to him?
这是规矩，干任何事都得预先请求。
You know the rules Mike. You have to ask in advance.
求你了！求你了，让我去波拿家吧。
Please Oh please can I go to Boners house?
我看今天晚上让你留在家里你会
Maybe staying home tonight will teach you how
知道该怎么做的。
and when to ask for something.
什么？我看你们这样做也太过分了。
I don't. You guys have gone too far this time.
我会怎么样？
You know what I'm going to do?
那我事先就告诉你们吧。
I'm going to tell you what I'm going to do.
(stands on his head)
不让我去波拿家，我就一直倒立着。
I'm going to stay like this until you let me go to Boner's house.
你们看着办吧。
How do you like that?
这样你可以用充到大脑里的血好好想想。
Well maybe all that blood rushing to your brain will do it some good.
你在干什么我亲爱的哥哥？
What didn't they let you do this time?
抗议不让我去波拿家。
Spend the night at Boners.
简直难以相信，安妮一块到我们家来了，
I can't believe this. Annie Boyers sleeping at my house,
而我这位傻哥哥还一直倒立着。
and my stupid brother is sitting on his head.
我就喜欢这么呆着。
Yeah! And I'm going to stay just like this.
妈妈，妈妈……
Mum! Mum!
什么事？又是什么事？
What? What is it?
是他！
It's him.
我什么事也没干，妈妈。
I didn't do anything mum.
也许该用橡皮把Carol的房间钉满才是。
Maybe it's time we wallpaper Carol's room in rubber.
我要失陪了，去给波拿打个电话，他会伤心的。
Now if you'll excuse me,I have to call Boner and break my best friends heart.
干嘛让我摊上这么个哥哥。
Why does he have to be related to me?
我为什么没有一个不会让我难堪的兄弟呢。
Why can't I have a normal brother who's not a total embarrassment?
嗨，所以我才出世。
Hey! That's what I'm here for.
很抱歉，波拿，
Boner,look I'm sorry.
我实在不能来了。
I just can't make it alright.
我的家庭需要我。
My family needs me.
好的，让我问问。
Yeah alright. Let me ask.
爸爸？
Hey dad.
你就忙吧。
You're busy.
会有办法的，
Yeah Bone,it should be fine.
要是不行我再打电话给你。
I'll call you if there's a problem.
好吧，再见。
Ok bye.
做得很好。尝尝？
These are good. You want one?
不，谢谢爸爸，
No thanks dad.
关于今晚的事情，我想……
Ah about tonight. I'd really..
今晚
About tonight.
你听着，
Would you please do me a favor
希望你今晚上千万别让你妹妹感到尴尬好吗？
and try not to tease your sister tonight,ok?
Carol?
Carol？
你有几个妹妹？
Yeah,that sister.
她有了个新朋友，
She's got a new friend,you know.
你就体谅她一下好吗？
So try to be a little sensitive ok?
男人一般都粗线条不会体谅人。
Hey dad,guys are supposed to be tough,not sensitive.
是吗？那么请问艾拉·毛瑞呢？
Oh really? Well then explain Allan Alder?
不知道。
I can't.
我告诉你个小小的秘密，
Let me let you know a little secret Mike.
女人就喜欢体谅人的男人。
Women go crazy for sensitive guys.
你就别骗我了。
Oh come on dad.
还记得那几部著名电影吗？
Yeah,you remember those classic movies
我强迫你去看的？
I bought and I forced you to watch?
怎么了？
Yeah.
记得卡萨布兰卡？
You remember Casablanca?
有个大舌头老头的那一部？
Yeah with that old guy with the lisp.
他叫柏戈特，最后你母亲和
Bogey,yes. Well do you remember how Carol
Carol哭了，你记得吗？
and your mum cried at the end?
记得。
Yeah.
她们哭了像其他女人一样，
Well they cried,as all women do,Mike.
并不是因为柏戈特是个坚强的人，
Not because Bogey's a tough guy,which he was,
而是因为他很体谅人。
but because he was also sensitive.
体谅人？
Sensitive huh?
嗯。
Uhm!
我是为了你着想，孩子。
Here's looking at you kid.
要多练。
Needs work.
（门铃响）
(door bell)
再见妈妈再见爸爸，回头见。
Bye mum! Bye dad! See you later.
Carol，等一下。
Carol,wait!
Hi Carol.
这就是我母亲，安妮。妈妈，这就是安妮。
Annie,this is my mum. Mum This is Annie.
很高兴见到你。Jason……
Nice to meet you Annie. Jason!
我也很高兴。
Thanks. You too.
这是我的小弟弟BEN。
And this is my little brother,Ben.
又带了衣服给Carol吗？
Did you bring more clothes for Carol?
Ben!
没关系，这样的弟弟我也有。
It's Ok. I have a little brother too.
这是我的父亲。
And this is my father.
HI，安妮，
Hi Annie.
Hi.
我很高兴见到帮Carol涂脂抹粉的艺术家。
Well it's nice to meet the artist who painted Carols face.
爸爸！
Dad!
没关系，这样的爸爸我也有。呵呵。
It's Ok. I have a father too.
(cough)
这是Mike。
And that's Mike.
Hi.
回头见，Mike。
See you later Mike.
好，回头见。我得去换一套衣服，
Oh,yeah right! I have to go out and change.
因为刚才我在摆弄保时捷牌轿车。
I was just in the garage fixing the Porsche.
我们没有保时捷牌轿车。
Mike,we don't have a Porsche.
啊，对，保时捷、法拉力谁能分得清呢。
Ah right! Porsche,Ferrari,who can keep them straight.
来，这几件挺帅的套衫你试试。
Come on Carol. I brought over a couple of hot sweaters I want you to try.
好极了！
Oh,great!
我看今晚你们就呆在家吧。
So you guys can just hang around here tonight.
妈妈！
Mum!
穿这件你真是太性感了！
This one makes you look so sexy.
真的？！
Really?
你还想干些什么？
What do you want to do tonight?
不是说好逛商店吗？
Well I thought we were going to the mall?
可今天下午已经逛了。
Well we just did that this afternoon.
去西柏莱斯商店看看。
Well we could see something at the Six Blacks?
你想看什么？
Anything you want to see?
随便看看。
Not really.
我也是。
Me neither.
其实都看过。
I've seen them all.
我也是。
Me too.
还上哪？
Well,where else?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我也不知道。
I don't know either.
我看就别出去了。
We don't have to go out.
你是说呆在这？
You mean stay here?
是啊。
We could.
呆一晚？
For the night?
那不挺有趣吗？
Hey that would be fun.
对，哈哈。
Yeah!
Carol该有自己的朋友，
Carol's going to have her own friends
我们不必操心，除非有这个必要。
and we shouldn't worry unless there's something to worry about.
你和我意见一致的时候总显得那么聪明。
You sound so smart when you agree with me.
你别太得意了。
Don't push your luck.
糖蜡大虾？
Sweet and sour shrimp?
我尝尝。
Oh,is that for me?
味道不错。
(spits it out) It's good.
这怎么可能呢。
Ah,this can't be.
我是严格按照菜谱做的，
You know I followed that recipe to the letter.
水珠子跳得简直就像芭蕾舞演员一样。
I had water dancing like Baryshnikov here.
也许该用糖时你却用了盐。
Honey. I think you used salt instead of sugar.
这绝不可能。
Well that's impossible.
这也没关系。
Well that's ok.
每个人都可能这样。
I mean it could happen to anybody.
因为盐和糖看上去好象差不多。
It looks exactly alike. It's an easy mistake.
你也经常搞错。呵。
So you've done it too,huh?
你就别逗了。
You've got to be kidding.
你还是穿这种颜色好看。
This color would look good on you
比不上穿在你身上好看。
Not as good as it looks on you.
我看不见的。
Not true.
老实说你穿任何一件都好看。
Let's face it. All these look better on you.
Carol，我和爸爸去中国餐馆
Carol! Your father and I are getting some Chinese take out,
买几个菜回来。
from wok around the clock.
爸爸不是烧饭了吗？
I thought dad was..
是烧了。帮我布置餐桌好吗？
He was. Would you set the table for me please?
好的。你在这里呆一晚肯定不介意吗？
Sure. Are you sure you don't mind hanging out here all evening?
不。
No!
女士们。
Ladies.
Hi!
HI。
你有什么事吗？
what do you want?
什么事也没有，我来呼吸一点新鲜空气。
Ah,not a thing. I was just out for a fresh of breath air.
OH，你这衣服真美，安妮。
Vicious sweater Annie.
谢谢。听到男士的赞赏很高兴。
Thanks. It's nice to have a boy's point of view.
对，可不是吗，
Yeah,well,that's me.
我是男士，
All boy.
是个地道的男子汉。
Some might even say a man.
甚至称得上是体谅人的男子汉。
Some might even say a sensitive man.
你的话甚至使我马上就在呕吐了。
Some might even say I'm gonna puke on my shoes.
我很喜欢你这身衣服。
I like your outfit too.
哈哈，这个。
This?
当·约翰逊每个月都要给我送点料子来，
Well Don Johnson sends me these test clothes every month,
要我批准。
for my approval.
我看这料子可以评为一等。
I guess I'll give these a thumbs up.
Mike，你的鼻子里有东西出来了。
Ah Mike. There's something hanging from your nose.
Carol，我觉得你显然是希望我离开这，
Cool. I get the distinct feeling that you want me to leave.
如果真是这样，你就直说，
If you do,just say the word and I'll go.
我会的。
I want you to know,
我要告诉你你告诉别对他客气，别因为他是我的哥哥。
you don't have to be nice to Mike just because he's my brother.
好吧。
Ok.
我去布置餐桌。
I'm got to go set the table.
我换身衣服马上下来。
I'm going to change. I'll be right down.
好的。
Ok.
莎莉，我在哪里你猜猜看。
(phone call) Sherry! Guess where I am?
我在Seaver家。对，Mike Seaver。
The Seavers. Yes,and Mike's here.
我想他喜欢我。
I think he likes me.
他换了衣服还梳了头，
Well he changed his clothes and combed his hair.
Carol她一点也没有怀疑。
No,Carol doesn't suspect a thing.
快来，Maggie。
Come on Maggie.
我马上就来。
I'll be there in a minute.
Mike,Mike，我错了，
Mike,Mike Mike. I was wrong.
今晚你应该到波拿家去，
You should spend the night at Boners.
现在就走。
And leave now.
可是妈妈，几时才能温习这该死的功课呢
Hey mum. How am I ever going to learn that darn lesson,
我要是出门，
if I don't stay here tonight?
今晚我不认为你该温习什么了。
Well I don't want you learning any more this evening.
我认为你该去照顾你那位朋友。
I think you should go. Go and baby-sit your friend.
是的，但是妈妈。
Yeah but mum!
谢谢你Seaver太太。
Hello,thanks Mrs Seaver.
波拿。
Boner!
Mike你好。
Yo Mikey!
妈妈！
Mum!
波拿你来这干嘛？
Boner,what are you doing here?
我父母不准我一个人过夜，
Well my folks didn't want me to spend the night alone,
我来问Mike来这行吗？
so I asked Mikey if I could stay over.
他没告诉你？
He didn't ask.
不，他没有。
No! He didn't.
不错，我没说，我知道说了会怎么样，
No,no,I didn't ask him. We all know what that means.
肯定不会答应，
No asking no getting.
这样的教训我有过。
I'm only going to learn the hard way.
波拿老兄你得走。
Boner,my friend,you'll have to go.
噢，别走，我们都是凡人，
Oh no. But we're all human mike.
总有忘记什么的时候
We all forget things.
干嘛让你这无辜的朋友
I mean why should your
为我一时的糊涂而受罪呢？
innocent friend suffer,on account of saving me?
没什么关系，波拿受得了。
That's ok. Boner's tough.
不，我受不了。
No I'm not.
Mike！我不让他走。
Mike,I insist.
波拿，请你留下来让我们款待你，
Boner,please stay and enjoy the Seaver hospitality.
做点游戏，看看电视，不会让你干坐着。
Watch TV,play games,keep each other busy.
Maggie，你干嘛拉着他？
Maggie,what holding you up?
咱们走，Jason，今晚还有事呢。
Let's go Jason. We don't have all night.
于是我哭了，我爸爸问我什么事
So,I was crying,and my dad said "what's wrong?"
可我不好意思告诉他。
I was too embarrassed to tell him.
为了什么事？
Well what was it?
为了电视。
Something on TV.
不说了，你会笑话我的。
I don't want to tell you. You'll think I'm a ditz.
不，我不会的。
No I won't.
你保证不会笑？
Promise you won't laugh?
我保证不会。
I promise.
好吧。我看了告别亲人飞向远方的电视。
Ok. It was one of those long distance commercials.
那可不，我看了也会哭的。
Are you kidding? They make me cry too.
他们没有！你在笑话我？哪个？
They do not! Are you kidding me? Which one?
父亲和儿子。
The Father and the son.
就是这个我也会哭的。
Yes,that's the one I was crying about.
我觉得自己很愚蠢。
I feel so stupid,yep.
必须告诉Carol，因为她该知道。
And we have to tell Carol,because she has to know.
可又不能告诉Carol，
But we can't tell Carol,
因为说了她会非常伤心的。
because it would break Carol's heart if we tell her,
现在你明白我的意思了？
but we know she should know. Yes or no? You know?
我非常清醒。
Believe it or not,I do.
对安妮的看法我比你准。
I was right about Annie all along. You see?
现在可不是我们讨论谁是谁非的时候。
Oh,this is no time to talk about whose right or wrong.
我对的时候你总这样做。
Why do you only say that when I'm right?
我们先把熟菜买回来
Look. After we pick up dinner,then we'll come back,
再去警告Mike当心安妮。
we'll warn Mike about Annie.
到那时候也许能想出个办法来。
By then,maybe we'll have figured out a way to break it to Carol.
我们现在不能走。
We can't go now.
行了，Maggie，只离开几分钟，
Oh Maggie,it's a minute there,a minute back.
什么事也不会发生的。
Nothing will happen.
特别是有波拿在这。
Especially with Boner there.
Mike，快让我进去。
Mikey. Come on,let me in.
波拿，如果你真是我的朋友
Boner,look. If you're really my friend,
你就去艾迪家。
then you'll go spend the night at Eddies.
艾迪今晚有朋友。
Eddie's got a date tonight.
Mike，至少让我进去把睡袋拿出来。
Come on Mike. You'll at least let me in to get my sleeping bag.
好吧，可只给你一秒钟。
Alright,alright. But just for a second.
你这样对待我是因为你那妞？
This is so that you can make the moves on that chick,huh?
当然不是。
Of course not.
这样做太不漂亮了。
You know Mike,this is totally uncool.
她是你妹妹的朋友。哗。
She's your sister's friend and ...oh wow!
想说话？
You were saying?
Mike留波拿吃晚饭吗？
Mike is Boner staying for dinner?
不，
Ah,no,no. Actually,
他现在就走，去艾迪家过夜。
he's leaving right now to go spend the night at Eddie's house.
你非去不可吗？
You're sure you can't get out of it.
对，对，你要是不去，艾迪会很失望的。
Yeah,Eddie gets real disappointed. But thanks for stopping over,
谢谢你，星期一学校见。
and I'll see you in school on Monday.
Carol，你先去试试那件紫红的，
Carol,go ahead and try on the peach blouse I brought.
我忘了拿筷子了。
I forgot the chopsticks.
好吧。爸爸妈妈回来就叫我们。
Ok! Call us when mum and dad get back. Ok?
当然可以，没问题。
Yeah,sure,fine,no problem.
这种筷子好吗？
Are these the good chopsticks?
是我们家最好的。
Ah,best we have.
安妮，你这件很漂亮的
Ah Annie,that blue thing you have on there,
蓝的东西叫什么？
it's nice. What do you call it?
套衫。
Sweater.
很好，看上去很帅。
Ah good. That's catchy.
恐怕，它和我的耳环不配。
I'm not that this one goes with my earrings though.
耳环？
Ah,earrings?
瞧，觉得怎么样？
Here,tell me what you see?
对对，耳环挺好看。
Yeah,yeah,those are earrings alright.
跟我的套衫配不配？
But do they go with my sweater?
当然配。
Oh,oh definitely.
你肯定？
Are you sure?
为了肯定，让我再看一下。
Ah,well,just to be sure,let me double check.
我是希望今晚应该像这样。
Wow! I was hoping this night would end up like this.
Carol会回来的。
Yeah,but Carol might come back.
别管Carol。
Forget Carol.
你还真干脆！
Ah,I like your style.
安妮？
Annie!
Carol!
Carol！
Hey Carol!
OH，Mike，
很好。咱们谈谈。
Oh my god,we have to talk.
是吗？
Yeah!
这事令人吃惊。
Now I know this is shocking,
安妮在利用Carol，她感兴趣的是你。
but Annie is using Carol because she's interested in you.
不！
No!
是这样。我听见她打电话了，
Yes,I heard her on the phone
我想先警告你，免得出问题。
and I wanted to warn you before anything happened,
这种事情会使Carol很痛苦。
because something like this could devastate Carol.
对，这我知道，
Yeah. I mean yeah!
我看今晚我还是
You know,probably the best thing would be for me
到波拿家去过夜吧。
to go over to Boner's right now.
好极了。
Great!
再见，爸爸。
Hey see you dad.
你要去哪？
Where are you going?
去波拿家。
Boner's house.
什么？
What?
是妈妈的主意。
Mum's idea.
这究竟是怎么回事。
Don't give me that.
Carol，快开门。求你了！
Carol! Open the door. Please?
不！永远不出来，永远！
No. I'm never coming out. Ever.
也许不喜欢试穿的衣服。
She's trying on a skirt she doesn't like.
哦……
OoooK!
Carol，真对不起。
Carol,I'm sorry.
你给我走开。
Go away!
Carol，中国菜有了。
Carol! Chinese food.
中国菜中国菜，
Chinese food,Chinese food.
你真的要我吃中国菜吗？
You expect me to eat Chinese food?
好吧。
OoooK!
晚饭马上就要上桌了。
Dinner will be on the table in a minute.
记住，在远方。
Remember long distance.
哦。
Ohh!(sobbing)
朋友是至关重要的。
When a friend really matters.
我该和Carol谈谈。
I got to go talk to Carol.
别提什么中国菜。
Don't mention Chinese food.
我该出去了。
I got to go outside.
这些人都不对劲了。
I'm surrounded by loons.
波拿。
Boner!
Mike。我什么人也不打扰，
Mikey,I won't bother nobody.
就睡在这。
I'll just stay right here.
波拿，我吻了安妮。
Boner I kissed Annie.
好家伙，真是太有意思了。
Oh man! That's fantastic.
你疯了，这太可怕了。
What are you nuts? It's horrible.
你不是一心想这样吗？
But I thought that's what you were after?
波拿，我把妹妹的朋友当目标，这也算神气。
Boner,hitting on your sisters best friend is totally uncool.
你怎么想的？
Where have you been?
Carol看到了就奔上楼去了。
Boner,Carol saw us and she ran upstairs crying.
怎么回事？
Oh! So how was it?
指的是什么？
How was what?
你说的吻？
You know. The kiss.
我可不是那种吻一下就到处乱说的人。
Well,I'm not one to kiss and tell Boner,
私下说吧，
but just between you and me,
我觉得她还挺那个的。
it was pretty hot.
哗，学一个？
Wow! Show me.
我真傻，没想到你这样的人
I was so stupid to think that somebody like you
会交我这个朋友。
would want to be my friend.
可我是你的朋友。
I am your friend.
安妮，我一点也不傻，
Annie,I'm not stupid.
我的平均名次是4.0
I've a four point zero grade average;
我还是象棋小组成员，
I'm a member of the chess club,
又是美国未来核物理家协会主席。
and president of the Future Nuclear Physicists of America.
我知道你干嘛来了。
I know why you're here.
你说得对。
Ok,you're right.
可我发誓我真的也喜欢你。
But I really like you too. I swear.
电视使我感动的事我从来都没有对任何人说过。
I never told anybody about those long distance commercials before.
我知道我犯下了一个大错误，
Carol,this is the worst thing I've ever done.
即使你永远恨我我永远也不怪你。
If you hate me forever,I don't blame you.
那好，我恨你。
Fine,I will.
不过我还有一个问题。
Just one question though.
你说吧。只要我能够弥补就行。
What? Anything to make it up to you.
为什么找Mike？！
Why Mike?
他挺帅！
He's cute.
笑话。
Yuk!
可他吻起来比谁都笨。
But he can't kiss for a doodlely.
你这样说是想让我好过一点。
You're just saying that to make me feel better.
对，是这样。
Yeah,I am.
Carol一定发现安妮的用意了。
Somehow Carol must have found out what Annie was up to.
咱们快上楼看看。
Well we'd better get up there and check on them.
我本来就是那样说的。
That's what I've been saying all along.
你同意了？
So you agree?
我说的当然同意。
Of course I agree. I said it.
Jason，现在不是讨论归功谁的问题。
Jason,this is no time to be claiming credit.
Carol!
Carol？
宝贝，你没事吧？
Sweetheart,are you Ok?
(Noise of squealing)
Jason，她俩都疯了。
Oh Jason,they are both hysterical.
Carol，安妮？
Carol! Annie!
我知道，爸爸，又是中国菜。
I know dad,Chinese food.
我对你说过没必要上来。
Told you there was no reason to come up here.
我不想伤任何人的心。
I didn't mean to hurt anybody.
女人迷上了我，难道能怪我吗？
Is it my fault that women find me irresistible?
那是你的不幸。
It's a curse.
那个大舌头的男人会怎么说？
Now,what would that sensitive guy with the lisp say?
他会说，我很抱歉。
I guess he's say "I'm thorry".
明白了。Carol，安妮，
I got it. Hey Carol,Annie,
能和你们谈一分钟吗？
can I talk to you both for a minute?
Uh hu.
好。
Yeah.
好吧，听我说，今晚发生了很多事情，
Alright. Now a great many things have happened to us tonight,
我知道该为咱们仨好好考虑一下了。
and I know that I have to do the thinking for all of us.
考虑什么Mike？
What is it Mike?
这样说吧，我可不会说什么高雅的话，
Alright,look! I'm no good at being noble Carol. But,
即使不是天才也能看得出三个年轻人的问题
it doesn't take much to see that the problems of three little people,
不等于一大堆豆子。
don't amount to a hill of beans.
对，请你们一定要记住，
Yeah,now you guys must remember this.
吻不过就是个吻。
A kiss is just a kiss.
Mike，还要说多久？
Mike,is this going to take long?
好吧，问题在于，
Alright look. The point is...
安妮，我很抱歉，对你吻没恶意。
Annie I'm sorry,but it can never be for us.
Carol，对你也很抱歉，我吻了安妮。
And Carol,I'm really sorry that I kissed Annie.
这事就别提了。
Forget about it Mike.
对，那没什么。
Yeah,it was nothing.
那没什么？
It was nothing?
这事就别提了？
Forget about it?
那干嘛还要哭哭啼啼的？
Hey,what about the tears?
还那么伤心？
The heartbreak?
吻一下又怎么样？
Hey what about my kiss?
有什么大惊小怪的？
What about Alan Alder?
（电视）我很抱歉，姑娘。
"Here's looking at you kid"
这个大舌头的人挺好。
That guy with the lisp is good.
你快看，她哭了。
Would you look at that. She's crying.
我真不明白，我做错什么了？
I don't get it. What was I doing wrong?
再放一遍，BEN。
Play it again Ben.